So today is a very special day because
I'm taking delivery of my first [__]
jacket. I know. No, it's not this one.
This one's old and ugly. What about that
one? No, that one's ugly, too. And
there's something missing. Can't you
tell? Oh, what am I doing? Oh, yeah.
That's right. I'm going. I'm going. I'm
living life right now. And this what
I'mma do it's over.
over.
[Music]
So, today's an even more special day
because it's actually my first time
seeing it in person since I bought it
and they decided to wrap it as a gift
for me, which is pretty cool. And now
that I'm actually owning the jet, I've
realized that I should have had it a
long time ago because at the beginning
of the year, my goal was to own a jet,
but I had a pink Bugatti and somebody
came to me with a crazy offer to buy a
second Bugatti. I said, "You know what?
What's cooler, a jet or two Bugattis?"
Said, "You know what? Two Bugattis." And
I bought a second Bugatti. But then
after having two Bugattis, I realized I
could only drive one at a time. And then
there I decided to do a challenge in
order for me to feel like I earned the
jet. So what I do, I live stream for
five weeks in a row showing every single
one of my trades with people live on
YouTube until I made a million dollars.
As soon as I made a million dollars,
that's an extra million that I had after
I then sell the pink Bugatti. So then I
can buy my first jet. So now I only have
one Bugatti and my beautiful [__]
jet. Enough. That's it. You saved a
million dollars for this. What do you
mean? That's a small jet.
How big is your jet, [__] Um,
so ladies and gentlemen, I want to
welcome you to my Lear 45 jet. This is a
2000's jet. All right. When I was born,
so were you, right?
Doesn't really talk much. They don't
have to. Big uh um let success be your
noise, not your words. Or more like let
your jet engine be the noise. Exactly.
So this is a Lear 45 jet. This is our
beautiful like this. This this to me
right here is the craziest [__] of a
face of the earth. Like you know what
are you going to say now? Huh? Huh? So
this is how you open the door to the
jet. I actually didn't know this until
like a week ago up. So this is actually
made for big people. Luckily I'm a big
guy. Push it all the way up. So this is
uh my first jet. So I had to kind of
learn all of these things. And you're
still learning. [__] Yeah. This handle.
Oh, forgot. Yep. So this is a It's not a
good look for you. I know. I know. I
know. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. I'm I'm still
a rookie in the game, right? It's it's
only my first jet. This is a light jet.
They have light, mid, super mid, and
heavy. Decided for my first jet to go
light. And I happen to get a really good
deal. This is a $3.2 million jet because
of the years, because of the hours. It's
a very low hour jet, very low landings.
The more hours a jet has, the more
landings, it's like the more miles and
the more years that a car has, for
example. So, I got a very low hours,
very low landings, which is really good.
This is the interior of my jet, which is
kind of crazy to say, right?
So, Jesus, I need a bigger jet, bro.
Usually, light jets don't have as much
seating as this one. This seats about 8
to nine people. Nine if you want to have
somebody in the bathroom. And the irony
of it is that light jets usually don't
come with bathrooms. A busy man has a
lot of duties to do. This shit's really
falling
apart. Oh, so I guess um Velcro. This is
being held up by Velcro. I don't know
how that happened. I guess this is how
[__] happens. After you pay for
something, [__] always starts breaking.
But the cool of it is that there's
actually a bathroom and it works. Yo,
and I'm and I'm 6'2 and this is pretty
roomy for me. And I'm being 6'2 in here.
So, it's a really good
space. Thought I thought they would be
gold. And this is actually pretty cool
area back here. This kind of like these
little detail stuff that you don't know
until you actually get into this space.
But this is for where you would put your
pillows, where you would put your
blankets, light jets. Usually the
luggage would be in the back area where
the bathroom would be. Since this is a
bigger one, be able to have more space
for just normal stuff instead of
luggage. And actually, one of the main
crazy parts that people that buy jets
ask or they don't ask is where does the
luggage go? Cuz a lot of people think
just because you fly on a jet, there's
unlimited space everywhere. And that is
not the case. Luggage is a very big and
important thing because if I bring eight
people in the plane, that'll be anywhere
from 8 to 12 bags. This is actually a
flex. I have chartered many jets in the
past and these have been on some of them
and not a lot of them. The cool part of
it is that it comes in every single
area. And then we have like one big
Monopoly table. I could imagine like an
Instagram post of you with a computer
right there. Yeah, like that. I think
I'm going to take that feature in the
future. Boy, if you don't Another really
cool feature is all of this overhead
lighting is actually ambient lighting.
So, it could turn into cool different
colors. Blue, red, green, purple. kind
of gives it a vibe when you're flying at
night instead of it just being pitch
black in here. So, that is a huge pro. I
do want to change these curtains because
they are very flimsy and they tend to
break. This one right here, it is a
little bit broken right here and when
you put it up, it kind of looks a little
bit ugly. So, I want to change them into
maybe just a like a like a more of a
gray color so it actually covers more of
the sun coming in. We should see the
emergency air mask. I think that would
be cool to show the audience. this. No,
that's not actually If this were to
actually deploy right now, if I were to
like take it off accidentally, that
would not be fun to put back on. I would
have to call my pilot. So then he calls
the mechanic. So he comes, charges me 10
grand to make sure they're all still in
service and put them back on. No, I'm
good. I'm good. And funny enough, this
right here is actually my seat. This is
the owner seat of when you're on a jet.
You're able to see the pilots exactly
how they're doing. You're able to be
accessible to the emergency door and you
have the right away to your guests in
the back. This is the actual seat. If
you're too close to the bathroom,
somebody's using it. You're being
disturbed. And if you're backwards to
your pilots, you can't really see what
they're doing. What if they [__] fall
asleep while you're flying? That would
not be safe for fun. Another really cool
feature is we have a 115 volt. So, you
can charge your phones directly with
whatever you would put in the wall in
America. I know you guys in Europe or
London have different outlet. Yeah,
different outlet. But yeah, it's
actually pretty cool because there's
only one on the whole entire plane. And
that's supposedly an added feature that
when they made it back in the day, it's
an extra 20 30 grand to run the wiring
to that point right there. I mean, for
the 2000, this was crazy, bro. I was
born probably the same time this was
made. And then we just meet in the
future 24 years later. Isn't that Isn't
that [__] insane? So, making it over
here to our bar area. I mean, I don't
really drink. It's kind of for snacks
and just to have kind of cups, napkins.
This right here is the TV. So, here
we'll have when the plane's on, the GPS
of where we're flying to, our time or
ETA, and when we're flying, I just pull
up here, turn on whatever lights I want
to turn on, turn them off, kind of
function the whole entire plane,
basically from this area right here. But
now, moving over to the most important
parts, the cockpit. How the [__] do I
even get in here? Am I supposed
to Oh, no. No. I would have got in
there, dude. How do these guys even get
in here, bro? because they're probably
not big guys like you, dude. Right. I'm
6'2, bro. Imagine if they were bigger
than me. I don't think they'd be able to
fly.
Dude, dude, you can't be fat and be a
pilot. There's just no way. So, moving
into the second seat. Holy [__] bro.
Look how they both move. I did not I did
not know that, bro. So, why do I Why am
I paying for two pilots? I got into this
whole buying a jet not concerning about
this at all. There is so many different
buttons, so many different options in
here that it's a bit overwhelming,
honestly. The amount of function. Oh,
we're going to have to get this guy a
new headphones. Well, I don't really
know anything about here in the front,
honestly. What the hell is this? Is this
the Oh [__]
handle. Is this the Oh [__]
handle. Hold on, [__] Yo, what
the hell? Oh no, dude. That's to get in
and out of here, bro. It's not the Oh
[__] handle. Yo, this this feels like it
shoots something. Like if I were to
click this button right here, like if I
were to just click this button right
here, I feel like
it Let me not potentially break
something. Let me get out of here. So
the inside's cool, but the outside is
really where it makes all of this come
together because without this one piece
of equipment, there would be no
functionality of anything that we're
doing here at all. It's this the wing. I
mean, of course, you kind of need that.
No, bro. It's what's under the wing.
Sometimes it's not what's on top, it's
about what's under. Oh, like you're
saying it's made out of like carbon
fiber. No, dude. This beautiful and
forget under. Yo, honestly, this is
probably the most important part because
when the haters are looking to hate,
they're going to be looking up from me.
You're like, "Where's this [__]
motherfucker?" Oh, that's him right
there. You're going to see me set and
forgetting in the [__] air. And there
is nothing you can do about it.
Actually, there's You could probably
shoot me down and that would not be fun.
The fact that you can identify me in the
air is actually kind of concerning. Some
people were telling me they're like,
"Hey, when you posted the jet, you
should have never put the tail number."
And I said, "Bro, I have nothing to
hide. Like, it's my jet. You can track
me. You can know where I'm at, wherever
I'm at." What are you going to tell your
wife?
Which one? What do you think about that
one? Which one? Oh, all of them. So,
this right here, this is actually an
added feature which costs an extra $200
to $300,000 depending on the plane. The
the STL logo. No, the the fin. Oh. Or
the you know, like how sharks had the
fin. Yeah. This right here is kind of
like a shark fin, but for the wing. This
supposedly makes it have more of a
narrow feel to it. Well, not narrow. So,
we can do like flips and stuff. No, no.
We No, no, no. We can actually just make
sharper turns because of this little
different fin add-on that we have here.
This I guess that's cool. Makes us look
cooler. Honestly, all all facts, right?
No. Yeah. I'm saying that this is an
added [__] cost to have this, right?
A lot of airplanes, they come with it,
but this one cost an extra $2 million
per one, right?
Just tell them that we paid an extra 2
million per wing because of that. You
you can say the airplane is more because
it has this. So it cost an extra 2
million because of So moving on to the
outer part of the wing, we have our
other beautiful segment of Saturn.
Diamond diamond. This is called a
winglet. Oh, this is a winglet. Winglet.
It's not like a shark fin. No. Winglet.
Winglet. Winglet. Okay. What the hell is
this? That's a 500k option. Yeah. This
cost $300,000 per each one, right? No.
So you can say you can say 150 each.
150,000 each for each one of these
little options that we added here. Oh,
you're so rich, bro. I'm ultra rich. So,
moving on to basically the most
important parts. The real most important
part are our engines. Without these
engines, pretty [__] And the only
reason why I bought this jet is because
these engines are under MSP Gold. XRP
Gold? No, no, no. MSP Gold. So, you're
telling me I should put my life savings
in XRP gold? No, no, don't do that. put
your life savings in my pocket. I'll
take I'd rather take your money. So,
what MSP Gold is, it's basically a
factory extended warranty, which they're
basically constantly getting serviced
and whatever breaks down on it, we're
paying monthly in order for it to just
get serviced right away. So, it's
basically insurance for the engines.
This is what keeps us safe. This is what
keeps us in the air. Without this,
there's no traveling. There's no
anything. We basically have brand new
engines 24/7. So, moving on to this area
over here. This is where the luggage
goes. So, not even the hawkers. Hawkers
is like that gray one right there, which
by the way, I did want a black jet. And
I'm so glad I didn't because we would
probably literally cook inside. So, this
actually helps with the heat. This is
where all the luggage goes. So, even a
big hawker like that does not have a big
storage like this on a light jet. We can
put a lot of luggage in here. You'll be
surprised how much stuff can fit inside
of here. Bro, we could definitely put
some of the haters in there. Oh, no. We
could put the haters in there and some
product. You know what I'm talking
about. Some some hair product for for my
hair. Moving back over here. This is the
the rear fin. You know how the sharks
have like the tail in the back? Is it
the tail or the fin? Tail fin. The tail
fin. This is the tail fin of this plane.
And the cool part is we have two of
them. I wouldn't really be able to tell
you why. And the cool part is but like
look at this dude. This shit's massive,
bro. Look at this. Honestly, I don't
really know how anything works back. Now
on to this side. There's actually a
really cool feature which I don't know
which one it is. I don't know if it's
that thin up there or if it's one of
these antennas, but the plane actually
has Wi-Fi. It's not a Starlink. It's a
different type of Wi-Fi that's for
aviation, which we pay an extra 5k a
month so we can have Wi-Fi on the plane
24/7 whenever we want. Yeah, I think
they're repoing your your plane there,
bud. No, no. This is uh I think this
controls that. You won't do it.
Wait, wait, wait, look, look, look.
You're going to tell
me. Oh,
what has the world come to? Whoa. They
didn't let me get my pilot's license, so
I got my own
uh, you know, RC license here. Come on.
Bro was the first guy ever to walk the
jet. Come on. Come on. In the front
here. Come on. We have some PPF on the
front just in case if uh some of the
bugs kind of get on it or birds or
haters, it could just, you know, kind of
just fly off because uh we don't want to
keep the head of our beautiful aviation
dirty wiz. Oh [__] The tip of the
carpet. The tip of the So the buying
process of this plane was actually
something that was very different than
what I'm used to. Usually when I want to
buy a car, I want to buy a watch, I just
go and buy it, right? But obviously
something this big, there's a lot of
things that I don't know about it. I'm
not part of aviation. So first thing
that I did, I got the lawyer, which one
of my friends helped me out with. I put
about 200 grand into the escrow, which
is basically like a deposit to show that
I'm serious. And then before I actually
buy the jet, it has to go through a
pre-purchase inspection where I had to
pay this dude 20,000 or 21,000 for him
to go out and just inspect the whole
entire plane. It was a big booklet this
big that he has to go to do every single
part of the aviation. Like I'm talking
about every single one of these screws,
everything of the plane, this handle,
the seat. He has to do a pre-person
inspection of the whole entire plane.
You have to take it for a test flight,
make sure everything works. And that
took probably 3 weeks by itself. I don't
know if that was a long little bit of
time, but when the pre-purchase
inspection came back, the I think it was
the real thrusters or something with the
engine in the back had an issue because
it just didn't close or something. And
that took about another week and a half
to get fixed. And then after that, bye.
Had to get the pilots. Luckily, the
pilots are not on salary. I basically
pay them per flight. Storage, my friend
owns this place where all these hangers
are at. So, I get a really good rate.
Keep it inside, outside. It's a mix of
both. Fuel is really good as well
because we fuel up here. And the crazy
part is the continuous expenses of
having the plane. There's basic
insurance I have to constantly be
paying. There's routine maintenance that
has to get done every single time. And
preventative inspections like before you
were to take a long flight. Whatever you
just checked on the last flight, you got
to check it again. And even if, for
example, let's say that this screw right
is not damaged, but it's already past
the time of where it it's not good
anymore. I have to buy the screw again.
even though it's perfectly fine. So,
there could be a certain piece of
machinery in the plane that works
perfectly fine, but it's a preventative
type of inspection and just [__] in
aviation that you got to change it no
matter what because it's prone to the
breaking. It's just crazy stuff that I
did not really know as I was getting
into it, but I was in so deep already
that I said, you know what, I I got to
do it. It's crazy because I'm only 24.
Yep. I am only 24 years old and I own a
jet. And it's concerning to a lot of
people how I actually did that. Very
concerning. You actually own the jet.
Yes. And that's exactly why I wanted to
break this third fourth barrier because
there's a couple of
hat, you know, let's not call them the h
word. Let's call them truthers, right?
The people that that that think they
know the truth of stuff. And I you know
what? I don't I don't think they're
haters. I think they're just people that
don't believe in new levels just because
they don't believe it for themselves.
They don't believe somebody else can do
it and they find any reason to make that
unreality a reality for them. A couple
people have searched up online the tail
number which is November 7008 Sarah Papa
and have found public information on the
plane and does not come back registered
to me because I am 24 years old and the
company that I did the contract with to
own this plane is a brand new company.
Just in case you didn't know, insurance
on a plane is very expensive. And as a
24 year old that has $10 million in
liability in cars with three total
losses, two cars on fire, it's not a
good look. So my insurance would have
pretty much been almost quadruple the
price. So that's one reason why my
information doesn't come up anywhere
because I didn't owner finance with the
owner. So all of the information stays
in-house private until I fully own this
plane. And another reason why I didn't
do the full public transfer is because
the plane right now is parked 135
licensed. So I can do all the correct
way of chartering it where I'm fully
compliant and I can charter it without
an issue. If I change registration,
change ownership, I would have to do
another inspection, something very
small. But things can get complicated
and it's already part 135. I rather
leave it like that. It's actually even
better for me because all my information
stays more private. I'm already as out
there as it gets. With that being said,
back to the video. Oh, the shoes. I I
wore these shoes for a reason. I'm sure
everybody knows these are Vans. So, I
bought these Vans about four and a half
years ago. This is the first purchase
that I ever made with my trading
profits. Like, it's actually these same
exact Vans, and they've barely been worn
because I just remembered why I never
wore them cuz they give me blisters in
the back. And I hate wearing socks with
them. Well, you know what it is? From 7
years in a journey, 2 years losing money
consistently to then where after 2 and
1/2 years, I make a little bit of money
in my first purchase with a pair of $40
Vans. And then 4 years later of doing
the same [__] over and over again, I'm
wearing the exact same Vans to my
[__] jet. I did not think this was
going to happen this fast. I did not buy
these Vans with the intention of wearing
them. I did not buy these Vans with the
intention. my neighbor.
Hey, how rude. How rude of my neighbor,
bro. That's how rich people be. How rude
of that [__] taking off in his
jet while I'm talking, saying that the
motivation. But like I was saying, when
I bought these vans, my intention was to
never wear them to my jet. I bought them
because that's what I wanted at the time
and it's what I thought was a big deal.
And now I'm here. And it doesn't feel
real sometimes because it happened all
so quick. And when you have your head
down every single day, you don't really
realize the progression you're making
until you kind of have stuff like this
that make you realize how far you've
come. This was a big deal for me at one
point buying these shoes to now where I
have this. And it's not about I had
money to buy these shoes all along, but
it was more of the hard work that I put
in was from trading. And I bought these
shoes from trading. And I bought this
from trading. So that is what makes it
more powerful than anything is how I
actually obtained it through my work,
through my journey and my risk on my
trades. That is what it's about. Not
about $40 shoes. It's about the meaning
behind it and how I actually got it. And
it's crazy to me that I can pull up to
one of these places now and be like,
"Yep, my jet is here." Because I
remember like I wanted to have a jet
since 2 years ago when I started
chartering jets. I was paying 40, 50,
$60,000 for a round trip. Like, bro,
what if I just buy my own? I'm going to
literally save so much money that I'm
spending on just charterary jets. And
look at this here. I think I'm
personally one of the youngest guys to
own their own jet. Being a self-made,
successful entrepreneur, trader,
whatever you want to call it. I have
people in here that are 70 years old and
they just bought their first jet. I
don't know how it makes them feel that
I'm 24 and now I have one. Maybe it
makes them happy. Maybe it doesn't. But
I'm [__] here. I'm coming after every
single one of my goals and I'm not
taking my time. I'm [__] doing [__]
I have my dream home that I'm going to
be building in the next 12 to 16 months.
I have a book that I want to finish
writing, which I started it, but just,
you know, I've never written a book
before. I don't really know how much
time it actually takes to write one. And
as soon as I finish that, that's going
to be huge. I have another goal where I
want to have students withdraw a little
bit over $10 million. Right now, all of
my students collectively have withdrawn
about 6 to 7 million verifiable
supposedly a little bit more, but we
can't really verify. It's just too many
students. And one of my main goals is to
be the best version of myself that I
possibly can. As a friend, as a mentor,
as a creator, as health, everything, my
goal is to just be the best that I
possibly can be. And if it costs me some
sleep, if it cost me some money, if it
cost me something, so be it. Because I
want to be able to live life to the
fullest of my potential and not live
with regret. You know what? I should
have done that. You know what? I could
have done that if I would have done
this. No, I am going to live life to the
fullest of my potential no matter what I
have to exchange for that. I know what
I'm capable of and I know I'm going to
achieve it. It's just simple. And that's
something that you got to fix because
right now you're using some [__] as
an excuse to not get to the point where
you want to be in life. You're saying,
"Oh, I have school or I have work or I
have kids. I don't have enough time.
That's [__] [__] bro. It's
[__] You're procrastinating what
you're supposed to do because of your
current situation right now. And it's
not letting you where you want to be.
And you setting a date like tomorrow to
start or setting a next week or once I
finish this overtime shift or once the
kids are here. That's all [__] bro.
You don't really want it bad enough. And
you're underestimating the potential of
who you can be and where you can go with
just having a little bit of sacrifice.
like not watching a late night show with
your wife in bed because you're
comfortable and because she wants to.
Get to [__] watching a video of
whatever you want to do. Get educated
and put in the work. Be somebody that
your kids or your parents are going to
look up to. Don't be [__] average and
don't put any [__] excuses that you
have a harder situation than somebody
else. We all have the same
opportunities. If you're watching this
video, you have access to internet and
on the internet the opportunities are
[__] endless. So, with that being
said, ladies and gentlemen, for those of
you guys that are new to the channel,
hit that like and subscribe button. I'm
telling you right now, buying this jet
is only the beginning of many of the
things that we're going to achieve. So,
you're either part of the ride or you
just sit from the sideline. Thank you
guys for watching this video. I'll see
you in the next one. This is a pretty
motivational segment, but there's an
important question. What, dude? Does a
Jeff lie?
I don't know. You tell me.
I know way too many people here right
now that I didn't know last year. Who
the are y'all? I swear it feels like the
last few nights we've been everywhere
and back, but I just can't remember it
all. What am I doing? What am I doing?
Oh yeah, that's right. I'm doing me. I'm
doing me. I'm living life right now,
man. And this what I'mma do till it's
over. Till it's over. It's far from
over.
[Music]